Akash Kumar

Computer Scientist

A computer engineer who is keen to build and develop a technical and research career as a recognized professional in the field of teaching and academics. Able to work on own initiative or as part of a team, and can deal competently with administrative duties.



WORDPRESS

DATA ENTRY

DATA ANALYSIS

- akashdodani36@gmail.com
- Karachi
- github.com/Akah2244

. +923022439076

SKILLS

MS OFFICE

TYPING

in linkedin.com/in/akash-lohana-40a059225

HTML

GRAPHIC DESIGNER

(O) instagram.com/akashkumardodani? igsh=MXR6andvZzMyaGZyeQ==

EDUCATION

Computer Science

Quaid-e-Awam University of Engineering, Science and Technology

12/2020 - 09/2024 Grade

Nawabshah

Hala New

Nawabshah

Got 3.67 CGPA

Intermediate

S.I Government Degree College

04/2017 - 04/2019

Grade

Got A Grade

PERSONAL POJECTS

COMPUTER OPERATOR

Invenotry Management System (02/2024 - 09/2024)

DBMS

Developed a web-based system for managing inventory, tracking stock levels, and processing orders in real time. Integrated features like automated notifications and userfriendly interfaces to enhance operational efficiency and reduce errors. Built using modern web technologies, ensuring scalability and ease of use

WORK EXPERIENCE

Graphic Desinger

Fiverr

04/2020 - Present

Nawabshah Achievements/Tasks

- ID Cards
- Social Media Poster
- Facebook Cover Image

Internship

Central Library Quest Nawabshah

worked on creation of barcodes and QR codes specially designed for library services.

Web Development Intern

TechnoHacks EduTech Official

06/2024 - 07/2024 Remotely

CERTIFICATES

National Freelance Training Program (NFTP) (06/2022 - 09/2022)

Successfully Completed the NFTP Training in Creative Design Domain Through Online batch 03 where I learn adobe illustrator and adobe photoshop

Government of Sindh (Trade Testing Board Sindh) (05/2018 - 08/2018)

Successfully completed the Office Automation at Image Computer & Tuition Centre, Hala New.

Government of Pakistan National Vocational & Technical Training Commission (NAVTTC) Prime Minister's Youth Skills Development Program (05/2023 - 08/2023)

On successful completion of the certificate course of Database Administration (DBA Track) in A Grade

ORGANIZATIONS

COMPUTER SCIENCE STUDENT SOCIETY (C3S) (04/2021 - 09/2024)

WORK AS A PRESIDENT

PAKISTAN ENGINEERS FORUM (PEF) (02/2021 - 08/2024)

WORK AS A DIRECTOR OF GRAPHIC DESINGING

LANGUAGES

ENGLISH

Professional Working Proficiency

SINDHI

Native or Bilingual Proficiency

URDU

Full Professional Proficiency